mage-world.com 2015-12-31

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Statement

We respect your privacy rights. This policy summarizes what personally identifiable information we may collect, and how we might use this information. This policy also describes other important topics relating to your privacy. 

### Information Collection

We will only collect personally identifiable information (such as name, title, company name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) that you voluntarily provide through our website or e-mail correspondence. We also collect general information (such as the type of browser you use, the files you request, and the IP and country from which you request information) to improve our website and better meet your needs. All of your personal information including credit card information and the ordering process are handled through our 256-bit data encryption Secure Socket Layer (SSL) connection.

### Use of Information

Before we collect any personally identifiable information, we will provide you with an explanation of any possible uses of your data. The information you supply will be used by us to send you any requested information of the products and services, fulfill your orders and respond to your inquiries. We may also use the information to inform you about new features, products or services if you explicitly instructed us to do so.

### How we protect and store personal information

We commit to protect personal information. We store your information on our secured server. We use SSL for the checkout process which help you keep your billing information safe. No credit card information is saved on our system. We don’t share your personal information with any other third parties.

You can always trust when doing business with MageWorld, we always try our best to procted our customers.

### Other Important Information

This web site may contain links to other sites. We do not endorse or accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites. Additionally, some of our Web pages may contain "cookies," - data that may be sent to your Web browser and stored on your computer. This allows our server to "recognize" you when you visit our Web site in the future. Most Web browsers can be configured to not accept cookies, or to notify you if a cookie is sent to you.

It may be necessary, if required by law or judicial or governmental investigations, to release your personal information.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. We will promptly reflect any such modifications in the Web page.
